questions = [
    {"question": "Plants can survive without water.", "answer": False},
    {"question": "The speed of light is faster than the speed of sound.", "answer": True},
    {"question": "Part of the brain controls body movements.", "answer": True},
    {"question": "All mammals give birth to live babies.", "answer": False},
    {"question": "A starfish can regrow lost arms.", "answer": True},
    {"question": "A day on Venus is longer than a year on Venus.", "answer": True},
    {"question": "A lunar eclipse happens when Earth is between the Sun and the Moon.", "answer": True},
    {"question": "Water boils at 90Â°C at sea level.", "answer": False},
    {"question": "Animals use colors to camouflage.", "answer": True},
    {"question": "Leaves take in oxygen during the day.", "answer": False},
]